usairwaysvacations.com 2005-04-21

# US Airways Vacations - Privacy Policy

|   
|  |  |   
US Airways Vacations' Web site Privacy Policy

| Introduction  
---  
  
At US Airways Vacations, we believe that it is extremely important to protect the privacy of  
our customers. We are providing this privacy policy to help you better understand the ways in   
which your personal information is gathered and used on the www.usairwaysvacations.com Web site. 

US Airways Vacations is operated by The Mark Travel Corporation. The Mark Travel Corporation and its affiliated technology and marketing agencies gather, store and process the information from the US Airways Vacations' Web site. They help US Airways Vacations use customer information to create and distribute products, specials, promotions and Web site features for our customers. US Airways Vacations, The Mark Travel Corporation and their affiliated technology and marketing agencies (hereafter "US Airways Vacations") will not sell or share your personally identifiable information with any third party company without your permission.

If you have any comments or questions regarding this privacy statement, please contact US Airways Vacations via our online Customer Service.  

Back To Top  
  
Information US Airways Vacations Collects  
Airways Vacations' Web site collects customer information in a number of ways: when you sign up to receive e-mails, when you book online using the US Airways Vacations online booking form and when you fill out a Customer Service request.

The types of information collected on these pages are: 

  * Customer Name 
  * Traveling Companions Name 
  * Mailing Address 
  * E-mail Address 
  * Telephone Number 
  * Credit Card Information 
  * Reservation Number 
  * Age Range 
  * Gender 
  * Travel Habits 

Back To Top  
  
How Your Information Is Used  
Guestbook  
When you sign up for this e-mail guestbook, US Airways Vacations will send you regular e-mails promoting vacation travel, specials, sales and other information. You may unsubscribe from the e-mail specials list at any time by accessing the unsubscribe link at the bottom of the e-mail or by visiting the unsubscribe page on our Web site. 

Online Reservation/Booking  
The information you supply when you book a vacation online is used to process and complete your online order. US Airways Vacations does not share this information with any outside parties except to the extent necessary to process your order (for example, credit card authorizations).  
Information you submit for the purposes of online bookings will not be used to subscribe you for the e-mail guestbook (unless you specifically opt-in for the e-mail guestbook by checking the appropriate box on the online booking form).

Customer Service  
The information you supply when you send in a Customer Service request is used to assist you with your request. It may also be used to help US Airways Vacations review and improve its products, promotions and customer service.

Information collected through all of the methods listed above may be used by US Airways Vacations to improve products, processes and customer service. US Airways Vacations may also use some/all of the information to create customer mailing lists and may occasionally send our customers promotional pieces or other mailings. Mailing lists compiled from the information you provide will only be used by US Airways Vacations for its own marketing and promotional efforts, and will not be sold or shared with any third parties.

US Airways Vacations may also use non-identifying or aggregate information to improve our Web site, track promotional success, and/or to share Web site usage information with our hotel, airline or other business partners. This information may include number of page views, visitor sessions, session length, hits, number of unique visitors, browser type, number of visits by each visitor, most requested pages, most accessed pages, top paths through the site, number of returning users. Not all of this information is shared with our business partners, but some aggregate numbers such as page views on a particular page during a particular time frame may be shared. However, no personally identifiable information about you will be shared with any third party.  

Back To Top  
  
US Airways Vacations use of IP Addresses and Cookies  
  
US Airways Vacations uses cookies to track visitors to our site. US Airways Vacations gathers the number of unique visitors as well as the number of page views each visitor makes. The information is used for promotional and marketing purposes only and in the compilation of web usage reports. The reports generated do not recognize any information specific to your location, or anything specific to your individual machine. Cookies are tiny files that are placed on the hard drive of your computer. Cookies do not extract private or personal information from your computer.   

Back To Top  
  
US Airways Vacations Commitment to Information Security  
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, there are appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. We use SSL (Secure Socket Layers) to encrypt and protect your personal information. We understand that this is vital in the exchange of credit card and password information.

Back To Top  
  
US Airways Vacations Commitment to Child Privacy  
Protecting the privacy of children is very important to US Airways Vacations. US Airways Vacations does not collect or maintain information from our Web site from those known to be under 13 years of age. No part of our Web site is designed to attract anyone under the age of 13. When online bookings are made, the ages of children traveling with an adult are collected so that the appropriate hotel room and pricing can be chosen for the reservation. The lowest age range specified on the guestbook sign-up form is "Under 18."

Back To Top  
  
How to Access or Correct Your Information  
You can access the personally identifiable information you submitted when you made an online reservation by viewing your password-protected reservation. You will be asked to enter both your reservation number and your password. It is the responsibility of the password holder to take reasonable precautions to protect his/her own password. Do not tell anyone your password or write your password down where it can be viewed by others. 

To correct, change, or unsubscribe your e-mail address from the US Airways Vacations guestbook, you can visit the unsubscribe page. First, unsubscribe your old or incorrect e-mail address. Then if you wish to re-subscribe, return to our guestbook sign-up page and enter your new information.  

Back To Top  
  
Opt-In Information  
If you wish to receive information about US Airways Vacations news, products, and specials via e-mail, you may sign up on the e-mail specials sign-up page. (Information you submit for the purposes of online bookings will not be used to subscribe you to the e-mail guestbook unless you specifically opt-in for the e-mail guestbook.) 

Information you submit through any of the online methods, including online booking, may be used to create customer mailing lists. US Airways Vacations may occasionally send our customers promotional pieces or other mailings. Mailing lists compiled from the information you provide will only be used by US Airways Vacations for its own marketing and promotional efforts, and will not be sold or shared with any third parties.  

Back To Top  

Notification of Changes to US Airways Vacations Information-Use Policies  
If at some future date, US Airways Vacations determines that it will change the manner in which it uses the information it collects on the Web site, you will be notified at least 30 days prior to US Airways Vacations making the change. You would have the option of choosing to continue or not continue to be a member of the US Airways Vacations database receiving e-mails, and you would have the option of unsubscribing. Information collected prior to any information-use changes would be managed according to the Privacy Policy in place at the time it was collected. Only new information collected online would be subject to any new information-use policies.  

How to Contact US Airways Vacations  
---  
If you have any questions or comments regarding the US Airways Vacations privacy policy, please contact US Airways Vacations via our online Customer Service.   
  
|  |  |  |
